translatorscafe.com 2003-04-15

# Translation Agencies Database TranslatorsCafe.com. Privacy Policy

At TranslatorsCafe.com, protecting your privacy is very important to us. Our goal is to treat the personal information you submit us with the utmost respect. This Privacy Policy explains how your personal information may be collected, used, or disclosed as a consequence of your activities on this Web site. We urge you to read it carefully.

By accessing, using and/or downloading materials from, or sending or posting materials to, TranslatorsCafe.com, you agree on your own behalf and on behalf of each entity on whose behalf you act, to the terms of this Privacy Policy and to the practices for the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as described here.

Please note that this Site is also governed by the Terms and Conditions of Use. We urge you to review the Terms and Conditions of Use before proceeding further on this Web site. 

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

**Anonymous browsing**  
You can visit this Web site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself, including your e-mail address. In this case, our Web server collects the URL, the IP address and the domain you used to access TranslatorsCafe.com, the type and version of browser and operating system you are using, and the Web site you came from. This information is used by us to measure the number of visits, average time spent, pages viewed, and other general statistics about visitors to TranslatorsCafe.com. We may also use this data to monitor site performance for systems administration purposes, to make this site easier and more convenient to use. 

**Cookies**  
Cookies are small pieces of data stored by your Internet browser on your computer's hard drive, which permit us to recognize you when you access this Web site. If you are browsing, a cookie is used to help us measure the number of visits, average time spent, pages viewed, and other statistics relating to your use of this site. If you are searching, a cookie is used to carry the search request data from the request page to the results page. This cookie, by itself, does not tell us your e-mail address or who you are. 

Please note that portions of this Web site will not function if your browser does not accept cookies. 

**Our Use of Cookies**  
To ensure we are publishing the content customers need and want, TranslatorsCafe.com collects aggregated site-visitation statistics using cookies. We do not track your individual use of the site, nor do we connect the pages you have viewed to your registration information.

When you visit our site, a cookie is placed on your computer (if your computer accepts cookies) and is read subsequently to test if your browser accepts it.

TranslatorsCafe.com also uses "session cookies". Our Web site will recognize that you are logged into the search pages as you move from page to page. Once you close your browser, this "session" data is lost.

Cookies may be also used by third parties (including advertisers) who may serve content and/or advertisements and collect information directly from visitors and may place or recognize cookies on visitors' browsers.

If you choose not to have your browser accept cookies from the TranslatorsCafe.com Web site, you will be able to view only static pages and will not be able to access the dynamic areas of TranslatorsCafe.com.
